Finding Aid for the Collection of 45rpm Sound Discs PASC-M.0175
UCLA Library Special Collections
Collection of 45rpm sound discs
1950-1988
UCLA Library Special Collections
PASC-M.0175
151.5 Linear Feet (303 boxes)
This collection consists of 45 rpm sound discs
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9934670773606533
Scope and Content
Archival collection of 45 rpm gramophone records housed in the UCLA Performing Arts Special Collections, Archive of Popular American Music.
- Blue Thumb BTA 208 - Capitol GF 3473. 57 Records. (Box 1, Folder unknown container)
  Scope and Contents note
  Blue Thumb BTA 208 - BTA 265
  BMC BMC 1003
  Bradley's BRAD 7614B
  Brunswick 55438 - 71037
  Buddah BDA 165 - 585
  Buena Vista F 343B - F385B
  Bumps 363-26
  Buzz 1149
  Calla C-174
  Camden CAE 108 - 109
  Camerica CAMS-2
  Canadian American CA 123
  Capitol GF 1919 - GF 3473
- Capitol 3481 - CCF 161. 52 Records. (Box 2, Folder unknown container)
  Capitol 3481 - CCF 161
- Capitol CCF 183 - 247. 9 Records. (Box 3, Folder unknown container)
  Capitol CCF 183 - 247
- Capitol CCF 256 - EAP 855. 25 Records. (Box 4, Folder unknown container)
  Capitol CCF 256 - EAP 855
- Capitol EAP 920 - EBF 517. 25 Records. (Box 5, Folder unknown container)
  Capitol EAP 920 - EBF 517
- Capitol EDM 283 - F 638. 21 Records. (Box 6, Folder unknown container)
  Capitol EDM 283 - F 638
- Capitol F1 662 - F3 547. 57 Records. (Box 7, Folder unknown container)
  Capitol F1 662 - F3 547
- Capitol FDM 595 - Challenge 45-1022. 35 Records. (Box 8, Folder unknown container)
  Capitol FDM 595 - ZB 2008
  Capricorn C 8021 - CPR 0043
  Carlton 512
  Casablanca NB 926 - 956
  Cash 1047-AAX45
  Cat C 1314 - 1996B
  CDC CDC-ST10A - DS11B
  CEV 37029A - 37038B
  Challenge 59072 - 45-1022
- Chancellor C 1063 - Columbia 40659. 59 Records. (Box 9, Folder unknown container)
  Chancellor C 1063
  Chaparral C 1001
  Chelan 96330-2
  Chelsea 78-0100 - CH 3004
  Chess 8027 - CH 2131
  Chimneyville 45-435
  Chrysalis CHS 2006 - CRS 2101
  Circus World
  Coed CO 591
  Colonial CR 501
  Colossus C 112
  Colpix CP 186 - 726
  Columbia 1-784 - 40659
- Columbia 4-40674 - 45618. 54 Records. (Box 10, Folder unknown container)
  Columbia 4-40674 - 45618
- Columbia 4-45657 - B 245. 35 Records. (Box 11, Folder unknown container)
  Columbia 4-45657 - B 245
- Columbia B 246 - DCP DCP-1004. 43 Records. (Box 12, Folder unknown container)
  Columbia B 246 - Gold
  Coral 60813 - EC 81074
  Cotton 62-104
  Crab Cooker GP 168
  Crewe 334
  Cricket C 51A - C 7109
  Crystallete T 312 - T 204
  CTI OJ 12
  Curtom CMS 0132 - CR 1978
  Dakar 616
  Dance Along 616 - 6115
  DCP DCP-1004
- Decca 9-6 - 153. 8 Records. (Box 13, Folder unknown container)
  Decca 9-6 - 153
- Decca 9-194 - 9-29843. 26 Records. (Box 14, Folder unknown container)
  Decca 9-194 - 9-29843
- Decca 29888 - ED 2124. 57 Records. (Box 15, Folder unknown container)
  Decca 29888 - ED 2124
- Decca ED 2124 - Dun Hill 4382. 66 Records. (Box 16, Folder unknown container)
  Decca ED 2124 - F1 1354
  Del Fi 57-101
  Delite DEP 561 - 559
  Deram 85023 - 85058
  Dial D 1010
  Disneyland LG 775
  Dolton DO 772
  Dome 1000B - 1001A
  Dot 134 - 17585
  Downey D 104
  Dun Hill 4026 - 4382
- Dynasty 625 - Epic E6 7008. 62 Records. (Box 17, Folder unknown container)
  Dynasty 625
  El Dorado 509
  Elektra E 45203 - EKS 45782
  Embassy 6136
  Embry 2121 - 5121
  EMI 3992 - 8177
  Enterprise 9038
  Epic 5-9111 - E6 7008
- Era 1000 - Grenn 14034. 63 Records. (Box 18, Folder unknown container)
  Era 1000 - 1013
  Essex EXP 107
  Evolution 1048
  Everest 19310
  Fantasy 641 - 736
  Faro 584X - 596X
  Felsted 8631
  Flashback 81
  Fontanna 1541 - TF 441
  Garret GA 4002
  Crescendo GNP 405 - 449
  Golden GP 620 - R 555
  Golden Touch 111
  Goldies D 2605 - 2766
  Good News V42105
  Gordy G 7099 - 7193
  Gothic 60X-003
  Grand 100 - 1005
  GRC 2046
  Gregar 71-0101
  Gusto 2004
  Guyden 2024
  Grenn 14007 - 14034
- Grenn 14036 - 14156. 47 Records. (Box 19, Folder unknown container)
  Grenn 14036 - 14156
- Grenn 14158 - Heaven 7002. 48 Records. (Box 20, Folder unknown container)
  Grenn 14158 - 17004
  Hallicrafters 1
  HappyTracks 502 - 508
  Harris 24103
  Harvest 3609
  Heaven 7002
- Hickory 1324 - I.R.S. 9926. 58 Records. (Box 21, Folder unknown container)
  Hickory 1324
  Hi Fi R564
  High Time HT 173
  His Masters Voice 670
  Hoctor 607 - 676
  Hi Hat 951 - 945
  MCA 60-125
  Hi Hat 951 - 995
  Hoctor 1634 - 1503
  Hot Wax 7003 - 7106
  Imperial 66027 - 2792
  Indian GP 335 - GP 334
  Invictus 9075 - 9081
  I.R.S. 9926
- Island 99996 - MGM K 37. 41 Records. (Box 22, Folder unknown container)
  Island 99996 - 15002A
  Jamie 1127
  Jay Barkay 508
  Jewel 121
  Jimmy McHugh 1B - 3123
  Jolly Roger 4516
  MCA 60178
  MDM M-1
  Meals For Millions 1746
  Mega 615-0050
  Memory Lane 5-2272 - 15-2319
  Mercury 3091 - 36401
  Metromedia MMS 194 - 206
  MGM 212 - K 37
- MGM K 53 - Hi Hat 944. 39 Records. (Box 23, Folder unknown container)
  MGM K 53 - K 64
  Mercury 70819 - 73678
  Hi Hat 930 - 944
- Hi 2064 -London LSF 17. 52 Records. (Box 24, Folder unknown container)
  Hi 2064 - 2274
  Hi Hat 856 - 930
  London LSF 17
- Hi Hat 801 - Mark 806. 47 Records. (Box 25, Folder unknown container)
  Hi Hat 801 - 855
  Love 5003
  Mac Gregor 3985 - RD 5000A
  Maiden Voyage MVS 120
  Mam 3601 - 3629
  Mark 806
- unspecified (Box 26, Folder unknown container)
  A-AHA
- unspecified (Box 27, Folder unknown container)
  AIR-ALP
- unspecified (Box 28, Folder unknown container)
  ALP-ANK
- unspecified (Box 29, Folder unknown container)
  ANK-ASH
- unspecified (Box 30, Folder unknown container)
  ASH-AXT
- unspecified (Box 31, Folder unknown container)
  B-BAKE
- unspecified (Box 32, Folder unknown container)
  BAKE-BARK
- unspecified (Box 33, Folder unknown container)
  BARN-BEAT
- unspecified (Box 34, Folder unknown container)
  BEAT-BELV
- unspecified (Box 35, Folder unknown container)
  BENA-BIDD
- unspecified (Box 36, Folder unknown container)
  BIGB-BLOO
- unspecified (Box 37, Folder unknown container)
  BLOO-BORE
- unspecified (Box 38, Folder unknown container)
  BOST-BRON
- unspecified (Box 39, Folder unknown container)
  BROO-BROW
- unspecified (Box 40, Folder unknown container)
  BROW-BUBB
- unspecified (Box 41, Folder unknown container)
  BUCH-BYRD
- unspecified (Box 42, Folder unknown container)
  CADI-CAMP
- unspecified (Box 43, Folder unknown container)
  CAMP-CARP
- unspecified (Box 44, Folder unknown container)
  CARP-CARW
- unspecified (Box 45, Folder unknown container)
  CARW-CHAN
- unspecified (Box 46, Folder unknown container)
  CHAN-CHEA
- unspecified (Box 47, Folder unknown container)
  CHEA-CHIC
- unspecified (Box 48, Folder unknown container)
  CHIC-CLAR
- unspecified (Box 49, Folder unknown container)
  CLAR-COLD
- unspecified (Box 50, Folder unknown container)
  COLE-COLT
- unspecified (Box 51, Folder unknown container)
  COMM-CONJ
- unspecified (Box 52, Folder unknown container)
  COOK-CREW
- unspecified (Box 53, Folder unknown container)
  CRIT-DARI
- unspecified (Box 54, Folder unknown container)
  DARI-DIAM
- unspecified (Box 55, Folder unknown container)
  DEEP-DEVO
- unspecified (Box 56, Folder unknown container)
  DEVO-DOMI
- unspecified (Box 57, Folder unknown container)
  DOMI-DRIF
- unspecified (Box 58, Folder unknown container)
  DRIF-EAGL
- unspecified (Box 59, Folder unknown container)
  EAGL-ELEC
- unspecified (Box 60, Folder unknown container)
  ELEC-EURY
- unspecified (Box 61, Folder unknown container)
  EURY-FARG
- unspecified (Box 62, Folder unknown container)
  FAST-FIRE
- unspecified (Box 63, Folder unknown container)
  FIRE-FLEE
- unspecified (Box 64, Folder unknown container)
  FLIR-FOUR
- unspecified (Box 65, Folder unknown container)
  FOUR-FRAN
- unspecified (Box 66, Folder unknown container)
  FRAN-FUNK
- unspecified (Box 67, Folder unknown container)
  FUNK-GATE
- unspecified (Box 68, Folder unknown container)
  GATE-GAYN
- unspecified (Box 69, Folder unknown container)
  GEIL-GIRA
- unspecified (Box 70, Folder unknown container)
  GLAS-GQ
- unspecified (Box 71, Folder unknown container)
  GRAH-GREE
- unspecified (Box 72, Folder unknown container)
  GREE-HAGG
- unspecified (Box 73, Folder unknown container)
  HAGG-HANC
- unspecified (Box 74, Folder unknown container)
  HANC-HAYE
- unspecified (Box 75, Folder unknown container)
  HAYE-HIGG
- unspecified (Box 76, Folder unknown container)
  HIGG-HOOK
- unspecified (Box 77, Folder unknown container)
  HOOK-HUMP
- unspecified (Box 78, Folder unknown container)
  HUMP-INDI
- unspecified (Box 79, Folder unknown container)
  INFI-ISLE
- unspecified (Box 80, Folder unknown container)
  ISLE-JACK
- unspecified (Box 81, Folder unknown container)
  JACK-JACK
- unspecified (Box 82, Folder unknown container)
  JACK-JAME
- unspecified (Box 83, Folder unknown container)
  JAME-JETT
- unspecified (Box 84, Folder unknown container)
  JIME-JOHN
- unspecified (Box 85, Folder unknown container)
  JOHN-JONE
- unspecified (Box 86, Folder unknown container)
  JONE-JOPL
- unspecified (Box 87, Folder unknown container)
  JOPL-KC
- unspecified (Box 88, Folder unknown container)
  KC-KING
- unspecified (Box 89, Folder unknown container)
  KING-KNIG
- unspecified (Box 90, Folder unknown container)
  KNIG-LABE
- unspecified (Box 91, Folder unknown container)
  LABE-LAWS
- unspecified (Box 92, Folder unknown container)
  LAWS-LEFT
- unspecified (Box 93, Folder unknown container)
  LEMO-LEWI
- unspecified (Box 94, Folder unknown container)
  LEWI-LOBO
- unspecified (Box 95, Folder unknown container)
  LOBO-LOVE
- unspecified (Box 96, Folder unknown container)
  LOVE-LYNN
- unspecified (Box 97, Folder unknown container)
  MACG-MANC
- unspecified (Box 98, Folder unknown container)
  MAND-MARK
- unspecified (Box 99, Folder unknown container)
  MARL-MART
- unspecified (Box 100, Folder unknown container)
  MART-MAUR
- unspecified (Box 101, Folder unknown container)
  MAYF-MCDA
- unspecified (Box 102, Folder unknown container)
  MCDO-MEND
- unspecified (Box 103, Folder unknown container)
  MEND-MILL
- unspecified (Box 104, Folder unknown container)
  MILL-MORG
- unspecified (Box 105, Folder unknown container)
  MORG-NESM
- unspecified (Box 106, Folder unknown container)
  NEVI-OLIV
- unspecified (Box 107, Folder unknown container)
  OLIV-PART
- unspecified (Box 108, Folder unknown container)
  PART-PLAT
- unspecified (Box 109, Folder unknown container)
  PLAY-RARE
- unspecified (Box 110, Folder unknown container)
  RARE-RIPE
- unspecified (Box 111, Folder unknown container)
  RITC-ROXY
- unspecified (Box 112, Folder unknown container)
  ROYA-SEDU
- unspecified (Box 113, Folder unknown container)
  SEDU-SIST
- unspecified (Box 114, Folder unknown container)
  SKAG-STAR
- unspecified (Box 115, Folder unknown container)
  STAR-SURF
- unspecified (Box 116, Folder unknown container)
  SURF-TEEG
- unspecified (Box 117, Folder unknown container)
  TEIC-TEX
- unspecified (Box 118, Folder unknown container)
  TEX-THRE
- unspecified (Box 119, Folder unknown container)
  THRE-TOMP
- unspecified (Box 120, Folder unknown container)
  TOMP-TUCK
- unspecified (Box 121, Folder unknown container)
  TUCK-TWIT
- unspecified (Box 122, Folder unknown container)
  TWIT-VANH
- unspecified (Box 123, Folder unknown container)
  VANH-VILL
- unspecified (Box 124, Folder unknown container)
  VINT-WALL
- unspecified (Box 125, Folder unknown container)
  WALL-WASH
- unspecified (Box 126, Folder unknown container)
  WASH-WHIS
- unspecified (Box 127, Folder unknown container)
  WHIS-WIER
- unspecified (Box 128, Folder unknown container)
  WILB-WILL
- unspecified (Box 129, Folder unknown container)
  WILL-WINT
- unspecified (Box 130, Folder unknown container)
  WINW-WITH
- unspecified (Box 131, Folder unknown container)
  WITH-WOND
- unspecified (Box 132, Folder unknown container)
  WOND-YARB
- unspecified (Box 133, Folder unknown container)
  YARB-YOUN
- unspecified (Box 134, Folder unknown container)
  YOUN-ZZTO
- I've got a right to cry; When I'm walking. ABC - Paramount. 10475. (Box 135, Folder 1)
  Fats Domino
- Just because; Why. ABC - Paramount. 45-9792. (Box 135, Folder 2)
  Lloyd Prince
- Born too late; Come on Joey dance with me. ABC - Paramount. 45-9934. (Box 135, Folder 3)
  Poni-tails
- Whispering grass; Just keep it up. Abner. 59-1109. (Box 135, Folder 4)
  Dee Clark
- I Hope you won't hold it against me; Little bitty pretty one. Aladdin. 45-3398. (Box 135, Folder 5)
  Thurston Harris
- Bop-ting-a-ling; That's all I need. Atlantic. 45-1057. (Box 135, Folder 6)
  Lavern Baker and the Gliders
- I'll never be free; You're the boss. Atlantic. 45-2090. (Box 135, Folder 7)
  Lavern Baker & Jimmy Ricks
- C'mon and swim; C'mon and swim - part 2. Autumn. 2. (Box 135, Folder 8)
  Bobby Freeman
- This I swear; Tomorrow. Calico. C 106. (Box 135, Folder 9)
  The Skyliners
- Susie - Q; Don't treat me this way. Checker. 8437. (Box 135, Folder 10)
  Dale Hawkins
- Over the mountain across the sea; My baby's gone, on, on. Chess. 1654. (Box 135, Folder 11)
  Johnnie & Joe
- Over and over; Rock-in robin. Class. C-2063. (Box 135, Folder 12)
  Bobby Day
- That's all I want; Say yes. Class. C-2090. (Box 135, Folder 13)
- Just walking in the rain; In the candlelight. Columbia. 4-40729. (Box 135, Folder 14)
  Johnnie Ray
- The loneliest man in the world; This little girl. Columbia. 4-42776. (Box 135, Folder 15)
  Dion
- Midsummer in sweden; Somewhere, my love. Columbia. 4-43626. (Box 135, Folder 16)
  Ray Conniff
- Skinny minnie; Sway with me. Decca. 9-30592. (Box 135, Folder 17)
  Bill Haley and His Comets
- Nobody's perfect; It might as well rain until september. Dimension. 2000. (Box 135, Folder 18)
  Carole King
- Whispering bells; Don't be a fool. Dot. 45-15592. (Box 135, Folder 19)
  The Dell-Vikings
- Crazy; Buzz - buzz -buzz. Ebb. 119. (Box 135, Folder 20)
  Hollywood Flames
- You'll never walk alone; I'm gonna sit right down and cry (over you). Epic. 5-9015. (Box 135, Folder 21)
  Roy Hamilton
- The right to love; Don't let go. Epic. 5-9257. (Box 135, Folder 22)
- Kansas city twist; Let's stick together. Fury. 1059. (Box 135, Folder 23)
  Wilbert Harrison
- Monster mash; Monsters' mash party. Garpax. 45-44167. (Box 135, Folder 24)
  Bobby (Boris) Pickett and the Crypt-Kickers
- Angel baby; Give me love. Highland. 1011. (Box 135, Folder 25)
  Rosie and The Originals
- Going to the river; Mardi gras in New Orleans. Imperial. X5231. (Box 135, Folder 26)
- La-la; Ain't it a shame. Imperial. X5348. (Box 135, Folder 27)
- Poor me; I can't go on. Imperial. X5369. (Box 135, Folder 28)
- When my dreamboat comes home; So-long. Imperial. X5396. (Box 135, Folder 29)
- Its you I love; Valley of tears. Imperial. X5442. (Box 135, Folder 30)
- I still love you; Wait and see. Imperial. 5467. (Box 135, Folder 31)
- Raunchy; Puddin'. Imperial. X5474. (Box 135, Folder 32)
  Ernie Freeman
- I'm gonna be a wheel some day; I want to walk you home. Imperial. X5605. (Box 135, Folder 33)
- You don't understand me; (I do the) Shimmy shimmy. King. 45-5373. (Box 135, Folder 34)
- Little girl; Love came to me. Laurie. 3145. (Box 135, Folder 35)
- I'm gonna dry my eyes; I have a boyfriend. Laurie. 3212. (Box 135, Folder 36)
  The Chiffons
- New Orleans; Please forgive me. Le Grand. 1003. (Box 135, Folder 37)
  U.S. Bonds
- School is in; Trip to the moon. Le Grand. 1012. (Box 135, Folder 38)
  Gary (U.S.) Bonds
- Food of love; Twist, twist senora. Le Grand. 1018. (Box 135, Folder 39)
  Gary "U.S." Bonds
- What a dream; I don't wanta wait. Le Grand. 1027. (Box 135, Folder 40)
- Release me; Don't feel rained on. Lenox. NX - 5555. (Box 135, Folder 41)
  Esther Phillips
- The flying saucer, part 1; The flying saucer, part 2. Luniverse. 101. (Box 135, Folder 42)
  Buchanan and Goodman
- I'm sorry; He's mine. Mercury. 71032X45. (Box 135, Folder 43)
  The Platters
- The Mystery of you; Only because. Mercury. 71184X45. (Box 135, Folder 44)
- Enchanted; The Sound and the fury. Mercury. 71427X45. (Box 135, Folder 45)
- Sea of love; Juella. Mercury. 71465X45. (Box 135, Folder 46)
  Phil Phillips with the Twilights
- To each his own; Down the river of golden dreams. Mercury. 71697. (Box 135, Folder 47)
- No one else but you; I love to love you. Mercury. 71746. (Box 135, Folder 48)
  Phil Phillips
- Hotel happiness; Still waters run deep. Mercury. 72055. (Box 135, Folder 49)
  Brook Benton with the Merry Melody Singers
- Let me love you tonight; Goodnight my love. Modern. 45x1005. (Box 135, Folder 50)
  Jessie Belvin
- The jerk; Forget me. Money. 106-A. (Box 135, Folder 51)
  The Larks
- Oh' pretty woman; Yo te amo Maria. Monument. 45-851. (Box 135, Folder 52)
  Roy Orbison and the Candy Men
- Rainy sunday; Young in love. Nasco. 45-6021. (Box 135, Folder 53)
  The Crescendos
- The little white cloud that cried; Cry. Okeh Rhythm and Blues. 4-6840. (Box 135, Folder 54)
  Johnnie Ray & The Four Lads
- Bongo rock; Bongo party. Original Sound. O-4. (Box 135, Folder 55)
  Preston Epps
- Oh, Susannah; Pony time. Parkway. P-818-B. (Box 135, Folder 56)
  Chubby Checker
- Let's twist again; Everything's gonna be all right. Parkway. P-824-B. (Box 135, Folder 57)
- Dancin' party; Gotta get myself together. Parkway. P-842-A. (Box 135, Folder 58)
- Feel it; It's all right. RCA Victor. 47-7927. (Box 135, Folder 59)
  Sam Cooke
- Baby, I love you; Miss Joan and Mr. Sam. Philles. 118. (Box 135, Folder 60)
  The Ronettes
- My baby's gone; Party doll. Roulette. R-4002. (Box 135, Folder 61)
  Buddy Knox with the Rhythm Orchids
- You can't stop me from dreaming; Jo-Ann. Roulette. R-4037. (Box 135, Folder 62)
  The Playmates
- Will you love me tomorrow; Boys. Scepter. 1211. (Box 135, Folder 63)
  The Shirelles
- What a sweet thing that was; A thing of the past. Scepter. 1220. (Box 135, Folder 64)
- Soldier boy; Love is a swingin' thing. Scepter. 1228. (Box 135, Folder 65)
- My boyfriend's back; Now. Smash. S-1834. (Box 135, Folder 66)
  The Angels
- The girl can't help it; All around the world. Specialty. 591. (Box 135, Folder 67)
  Little Richard
- Send me some lovin'; Lucille. Specialty. 598. (Box 135, Folder 68)
- True, fine mama; Ooh! My soul. Specialty. 633. (Box 135, Folder 69)
- She knows how to rock; Early one morning. Specialty. 652. (Box 135, Folder 70)
- By the light of the silvery moon; Wonderin'. Specialty. 660. (Box 135, Folder 71)
- Cold cold heart; It won't happen with me. Sun. 364. (Box 135, Folder 72)
  Jerry Lee Lewis
- You got what it takes; Don't leave me. United Artists. UA 185. (Box 135, Folder 73)
  Marv Johnson
- Let me love you; I love the way you love. United Artists. UA-208. (Box 135, Folder 74)
- The jolly green giant; Long green. Wand. 172. (Box 135, Folder 75)
  The Kingsmen
- Why do they always say "no"?; The Old piano roll blues. Abbey. G - 711. (Box 136, Folder 1)
  Lawrence Cook, His "Player Piano" and Orchestra
- Summer job; Sealed with a kiss. ABC - Paramount. 10336. (Box 136, Folder 2)
  Brian Hyland
- You'll want me back; It's all right. ABC - Paramount. 10487. (Box 136, Folder 3)
  The Impressions
- Long, long winter; Amen. ABC - Paramount. 45 - 10602. (Box 136, Folder 4)
- Hey little girl; If it wasn't for love. Abner. 1029. (Box 136, Folder 5)
- How about that; Blues get off my shoulder. Abner. 1032. (Box 136, Folder 6)
- On the horizon; Stand by me. Atco. 45-6194. (Box 136, Folder 7)
  Ben E. King
- Markin' time; Alley cat. Atco. 45-6226. (Box 136, Folder 8)
  Bent Fabric
- I'm blue; Find my baby. Atco. 45-6212. (Box 136, Folder 9)
  The Ikettes
- Tweedle dee; Tomorrow night. Atlantic. 45-1047. (Box 136, Folder 10)
- Tra la la; Jim dandy. Atlantic. 45-1116. (Box 136, Folder 11)
  Laverne Baker and the Gliders
- When I was single; My true story. Beltone. 45-1006. (Box 136, Folder 12)
  The Jive Five
- He'll have to stay; Under your spell again. Capitol. 4368. (Box 136, Folder 13)
  Jeanne Black; Jeanne and Janie
- Missing persons; Gone. Capitol. F3628. (Box 136, Folder 14)
  Ferlin Husky
- Rainy night in Paris; Only you. Capitol. F4165. (Box 136, Folder 15)
  Franck Pourcel's French Fiddles
- I never felt like this; Bella. Carlton. 504. (Box 136, Folder 16)
  Jack Scott with The Chantones vocal group
- Turn me loose; Stop thief! Chancellor. C - 1033. (Box 136, Folder 17)
  Fabian
- Oh Cindy; The Tijuana jail. Capitol. F4167. (Box 136, Folder 18)
  The Kingston Trio
- Mighty cold (to a warm warm heart); Tiger. Chancellor. C - 1037. (Box 136, Folder 19)
- This friendly world; Hound dog man. Chancellor. C - 1044. (Box 136, Folder 20)
- About this thing called love; String along. Chancellor. C - 1047. (Box 136, Folder 21)
- Liza Jane; Back to school blues. Checker. 934. (Box 136, Folder 22)
- Smoke along the track; Waterloo. Columbia. 4-41393. (Box 136, Folder 23)
  Stonewall Jackson
- Go-go-po-go; The theme from "A summer place". Columbia. 4 - 41490. (Box 136, Folder 24)
  Percy Faith
- Fool, fool, fool; Sorry (I ran all the way home). Cub. K9022. (Box 136, Folder 25)
  The Impalas
- Jumpin' jack; Walkin' to school. Decca. 9 - 30552. (Box 136, Folder 26)
  The Kalin Twins
- Three o'clock thrill; When. Decca. 9-30642. (Box 136, Folder 27)
  Kalin Twins
- My baby just cares for me; Tea for two cha cha. Decca. 9 - 30704. (Box 136, Folder 28)
  The Tommy Dorsey Orchestra Starring Warren Covington
- It's only the beginning; Oh! My goodness. Decca. 9 - 30807. (Box 136, Folder 29)
- Mother wouldn't do that; Funny way of laughin'. Decca. 31371. (Box 136, Folder 30)
  Burl Ives